Guide to the Walter Chauncey Camp Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1875 - 1925; Series I; 13 linear feet (31 boxes)
  - United Press Associations, 1911 (Box 25, Folder 694)
  - United States Attorney-General, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 695)
  - United States Committee on Public Information, 1918-1919 (Box 25, Folder 696)
  - United States Department of Agriculture, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 697)
  - United States Department of Commerce (*), 1917 (Box 25, Folder 698)
  - United States Department of Labor, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 699)
    Includes "Bureau of the Census: Men in the United States subject to selective conscription".
  - United States Department of the Interior, 1911-1923 (Box 25, Folder 700)
  - United States Indian School(*), 1896, 1906-1914 (Box 25, Folder 701)
  - United States Military Academy, 1893-1894, 1904-1914, undated (Box 25, Folder 702)
    Includes a report on athletics at West Point.
  - United States Naval Academy, 1893, 1906, 1909, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 703)
  - United States Navy Department(*), 1917-1920, 1923-1924, undated (Box 25, Folder 704-707)
    Folder 705 includes "General report on the Navy Commission on Training Camp activities."
  - United States Tariff Commission, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 708)
  - United States Treasury Department, 1917-1918 (Box 25, Folder 709)
  - United States War Department(*), 1900, 1912, 1917-1922 (Box 25, Folder 710-712)
  - University Club:
    - Boston, 1894 (Box 25, Folder 713)
    - Los Angeles, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 713)
    - New York, 1894-1895, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 713)
    - San Francisco, 1892, 1924, undated (Box 25, Folder 713)
  - University Review, 1893 (Box 25, Folder 713)
  - Unpopular Review, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 714)
  - Upton, J. D., 1894 (Box 25, Folder 714)
  - Utah, University of, 1900 (Box 25, Folder 714)
  - Utay, Joseph, 1916-1921 (Box 25, Folder 714)
  - Vail, A. H., 1906 (Box 25, Folder 715)
  - Vail, Fred C., 1905, 1907-1912 (Box 25, Folder 715)
  - Vail, Louis de P., 1894 (Box 25, Folder 715)
  - Vande Graff, A. S., 1912, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 716)
  - Van Duzer, Henry S., 1893 (Box 25, Folder 716)
  - Van Dyke, E. C., 1911 (Box 25, Folder 716)
  - Van Horne, Earl J., 1916 (Box 25, Folder 716)
  - Van Liew, John, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 716)
  - Van Pelt, John V., 1906 (Box 25, Folder 716)
  - Van Surdam, H. E.(*), 1908-1920 (Box 25, Folder 717)
  - Vance, Arthur T.
    See: box 27, folder 764
  - Vandenburg, Arthur H., 1908 (Box 25, Folder 718)
  - Vanderbilt University, 1899, 1910, 1919, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 718)
  - Vandercook, D. C., 1917 (Box 25, Folder 718)
  - Vanderpool, Wynant D., 1924 (Box 25, Folder 718)
  - Vanity Fair (*), 1914-1916, 1919, undated (Box 25, Folder 719)
  - Varnell, George M., 1910, 1916, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 720)
  - Vaughn, Howard F., 1920 (Box 25, Folder 720)
  - Veeder, Paul L., 1912, 1916 (Box 25, Folder 721)
  - Venable, Francis P., 1907, 1909 (Box 25, Folder 721)
  - Verbeck, William, 1905 (Box 25, Folder 721)
  - Vermont, University of, 1902, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 721)
  - Vernon, F. R., 1915, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 721)
  - Vetter, J. E., 1913 (Box 25, Folder 721)
  - Views, 1909 (Box 25, Folder 722)
  - Vigilantes, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 722)
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1909, 1914, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 722)
  - Vincent, George E., 1899, 1917, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 722)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1903 (Box 25, Folder 723)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1909 (Box 25, Folder 723)
  - Virginia, University of, 1890, 1892 (Box 25, Folder 723)
  - Vitilor Company, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 723)
  - Vogel, Martin, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 724)
  - Vogelsang, Alexander T., 1917 (Box 26, Folder 724)
  - Vogue, 1912, 1917 (Box 26, Folder 724)
  - Voigt, Charles A., 1900 (Box 26, Folder 724)
  - Wabash College, 1895, 1910 (Box 26, Folder 725)
  - Wade, John Ross, 1893 (Box 26, Folder 725)
  - Wadleigh, T. R., 1894 (Box 26, Folder 725)
  - Wadsworth, James W., 1899, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 725)
  - Wake Forest College, 1892-1893 (Box 26, Folder 725)
  - Walcott, Fred C., 1890-1891, 1902-1917 (Box 26, Folder 725)
  - Walden, Howard T., 1889, 1891-1892 (Box 26, Folder 726)
  - Waldo, C. A., 1894 (Box 26, Folder 726)
  - Waldron, Deane H., 1913 (Box 26, Folder 726)
  - Walker, Bradley, 1911, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 727)
  - Walker, Francis, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 727)
  - Walker, Francis S., 1894 (Box 26, Folder 727)
  - Walker, Fred M., 1917, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 727)
  - Walker, Hod, 1889 (Box 26, Folder 727)
  - Walker, Oliver D., undated (Box 26, Folder 727)
  - Walker, Stuart, 1909 (Box 26, Folder 727)
  - Walker, W. D., 1906 (Box 26, Folder 727)
  - Wallace, C. Brook, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 728)
  - Wallace, F. W., 1894 (Box 26, Folder 728)
  - Wallace, H. T., 1910 (Box 26, Folder 728)
  - Wallis, J. H., 1922 (Box 26, Folder 728)
  - Walradt, Arthur E., 1917-1918 (Box 26, Folder 729)
  - Walsh, Richard J.
  - Walters, R. W., 1912 (Box 26, Folder 729)
  - Walters, Raymond, 1914 (Box 26, Folder 729)
  - Walther,; C. N., 1909 (Box 26, Folder 729)
  - Waltman, Will D., 1902 (Box 26, Folder 729)
  - Walton, Alfred Grant, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 729)
  - Wanamaker (John) Company, 1917, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 729)
  - Wanamaker, Rodman, 1894 (Box 26, Folder 729)
  - War Camp Community Service, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 730)
  - Warburg, Paul M., 1917 (Box 26, Folder 730)
  - Ward, Henry Baldwin, 1917 (Box 26, Folder 730)
  - Ward, Henry C., 1901, 1903 (Box 26, Folder 730)
  - Ward, John A., 1916 (Box 26, Folder 730)
  - Warner, Glenn S.(*), 1898-1899, 1901, 1909-1921 (Box 26, Folder 731)
  - Warner, M. J., 1905 (Box 26, Folder 732)
  - Warren, F., 1894-1895 (Box 26, Folder 732)
  - Warren, Herbert S., 1903 (Box 26, Folder 732)
  - Warren, Ralph H., 1894, undated (Box 26, Folder 732)
  - Warum, C. F., 1894 (Box 26, Folder 732)
  - Washburn College, 1905 (Box 26, Folder 733)
  - Washburn, W. D., Jr., 1902 (Box 26, Folder 733)
  - Washington Agricultural College, 1901 (Box 26, Folder 733)
  - Washington & Jefferson College, 1917 (Box 26, Folder 733)
  - Washington, G. E., 1916 (Box 26, Folder 733)
  - Washington State College, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 733)
  - Washington University, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 733)
  - Washington, University of, 1917, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 733)
  - Washington, William D., undated (Box 26, Folder 733)
  - Waterbury, 1894 (Box 26, Folder 734)
  - Waterman, Cameron B., 1904 (Box 26, Folder 734)
  - Waterman, F. W., 1888 (Box 26, Folder 734)
  - Waterman, H. L., 1915 (Box 26, Folder 734)
  - Waters, Bertram Gordon, 1894, 1900-1916 (Box 26, Folder 735)
  - Waters, Charles Vinton, 1893 (Box 26, Folder 735)
  - Waters, R. J., 1906 (Box 26, Folder 735)
  - Watertown (New York) Football Team, 1899 (Box 26, Folder 735)
  - Watkins, George L., 1916 (Box 26, Folder 736)
  - Watkins, John Elfreth, 1911 (Box 26, Folder 736)
  - Watson, E. P., 1886 (Box 26, Folder 736)
  - Watson, J. A., Jr., 1902 (Box 26, Folder 736)
  - Watson, R. W., 1894 (Box 26, Folder 736)
  - Watson, Robert W., 1910 (Box 26, Folder 736)
  - Watts, R. N., 1903 (Box 26, Folder 737)
  - Waugh, O. L., 1916 (Box 26, Folder 737)
  - Wayland, Francis, 1900 (Box 26, Folder 737)
  - Weeks, J. H., 1914 (Box 26, Folder 738)
  - Week's Sport (*), 1889-1892, undated (Box 26, Folder 738)
  - Welch, Lewis S., 1917 (Box 26, Folder 739)
    See also: box 28, folder 781-790
  - Welch, Pierce N., 1905 (Box 26, Folder 739)
  - Weller, Charles H., 1905, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 739)
  - Wells, D. C., 1907 (Box 26, Folder 739)
  - Wells, E. H., 1912 (Box 26, Folder 739)
  - Wells, Philip P.
  - Wells, Stanfield, 1910 (Box 26, Folder 739)
  - Wendell, Evert Jansen, 1900-1901 (Box 26, Folder 740)
  - Wentworth, R. DeM., 1918 (Box 26, Folder 740)
  - Werner Company, 1906 (Box 26, Folder 741)
  - Wesleyan University, 1901-1923 (Box 26, Folder 741)
  - West, Edward, 1905 (Box 26, Folder 741)
  - West Virginia University, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 741)
  - Western Reserve University, 1903 (Box 26, Folder 742)
  - Weston, Thomas, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 742)
  - Wetherbee, James A., 1894 (Box 26, Folder 742)
  - Wetzel, H. E., 1909 (Box 26, Folder 742)
  - Weymouth, C. W., 1908 (Box 26, Folder 742)
  - Wharton, Charles M., 1893, 1918-1922 (Box 26, Folder 743)
  - Wheaton, Henry M.(*), 1910-1916, undated (Box 26, Folder 744)
  - Wheeler, A. W., 1883 (Box 26, Folder 745)
  - Wheeler, Benjamin Ide(*), 1894-1911 (Box 26, Folder 745)
  - Wheeler, Robert B., 1899 (Box 26, Folder 745)
  - Wheelman's Gazette, 1892 (Box 26, Folder 745)
  - Whiston, George T., 1900 (Box 26, Folder 746)
  - White, Edwin, 1905, 1910 (Box 26, Folder 746)
  - White, H. E., 1916 (Box 26, Folder 746)
  - White, H. S.(*), 1903-1907 (Box 26, Folder 747)
  - White, Herbert H., 1905 (Box 26, Folder 747)
  - White, Horatio S., 1895 (Box 26, Folder 747)
  - White, J. William, 1895-1900 (Box 26, Folder 748)
  - White, John S., 1894 (Box 26, Folder 748)
  - White, Paul A., 1909 (Box 26, Folder 748)
  - White, William, Jr., 1907 (Box 26, Folder 748)
  - Whitehead, Aaron Pennington, 1894 (Box 26, Folder 748)
  - Whiting, A. E., 1902, 1908, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 749)
  - Whitman, Charles S., 1917 (Box 26, Folder 749)
  - Whitman, Colden H., 1914 (Box 26, Folder 749)
  - Whitney, Caspar(*), 1889, 1895-1900 1927, undated (Box 26, Folder 750)
    See also: box 6, folder 162-181 See also: box 12, folder 328-333 See also: box 19, folder 520-523 See also: box 26, folder 738
  - Whitney, R. T., undated (Box 26, Folder 750)
  - Whiton, James M., 1902 (Box 26, Folder 751)
  - Whittemore, A. H., 1902 (Box 26, Folder 751)
  - Whittemore, James O., 1909 (Box 26, Folder 751)
  - Whittier, R. C., 1907 (Box 26, Folder 751)
  - Whitton, Frederick, 1905 (Box 26, Folder 751)
  - Wick, Henry C., 1907 (Box 26, Folder 752)
  - Wickes, Forsyth, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 752)
  - Wiggin, Frederick H., 1911 (Box 26, Folder 752)
  - Wilce, J. W., 1916, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 752)
  - Wilder, Amos P., 1894 (Box 26, Folder 752)
  - Wildman, Leonard D., undated (Box 26, Folder 752)
  - Wilhelm, Donald, 1910 (Box 26, Folder 752)
  - Wilhelm, William, 1909 (Box 26, Folder 752)
  - Will, William, 1909 (Box 27, Folder 753)
  - Willard, Harry K., 1902-1903, undated (Box 27, Folder 753)
  - Willard, Waldo W., 1894 (Box 27, Folder 753)
  - Willett, James P., 1902 (Box 27, Folder 753)
  - Williams, C. R., 1906, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 754)
  - Williams College, 1892 (Box 27, Folder 754)
  - Williams, Carl, 1910-1911, 1919 (Box 27, Folder 754)
  - Williams, Henry L.(*), 1892-1899, 1902-1920 (Box 27, Folder 755)
  - Williams, J. A., 1900 (Box 27, Folder 756)
  - Williams, John A., 1889 (Box 27, Folder 756)
  - Williams, John Skelton, 1917-1918 (Box 27, Folder 756)
  - Williams, L., 1911 (Box 27, Folder 756)
  - Williams, Laurence Staley, 1900 (Box 27, Folder 756)
  - Williams, Nathan G.(*), 1887, 1892, 1902-1920 (Box 27, Folder 757)
  - Williams, R. P., 1916 (Box 27, Folder 758)
  - Williams, S. C., 1911 (Box 27, Folder 758)
  - Williamson, C. G., 1913 (Box 27, Folder 759)
  - Williamson, P. B., 1917 (Box 27, Folder 759)
  - Willis, E. M., 1907 (Box 27, Folder 759)
  - Wilshire, George P., 1899 (Box 27, Folder 759)
  - Wilson, Alexander M., 1912 (Box 27, Folder 760)
  - Wilson, Harry W., 1908 (Box 27, Folder 760)
  - Wilson, James D., 1911 (Box 27, Folder 760)
  - Wilson, James F., 1893, 1910 (Box 27, Folder 760)
  - Wilson, Thomas W., 1878 (Box 27, Folder 760)
  - Wing, Henry A., 1908 (Box 27, Folder 761)
  - Winslow, Burnside, 1902 (Box 27, Folder 761)
  - Winslow, Samuel E., 1900, 1912 (Box 27, Folder 761)
  - Winston, Robert, 1894 (Box 27, Folder 761)
  - Winter, Wallace C., 1911, 1913 (Box 27, Folder 762)
  - Winters, Fred H., 1902 (Box 27, Folder 762)
  - Winters, William H., 1923 (Box 27, Folder 762)
  - Winton, Charles J., 1894 (Box 27, Folder 762)
  - Wisby, H., 1902 (Box 27, Folder 763)
  - Wisconsin Alumni Association, 1924 (Box 27, Folder 763)
  - Wisconsin Interscholastic Athletic Association, 1902 (Box 27, Folder 763)
  - Wisconsin, University of, 1910 (Box 27, Folder 763)
  - Witherbee, Walter C., 1902 (Box 27, Folder 763)
  - Withers, John P., Jr., 1890 (Box 27, Folder 763)
  - Woman's Home Companion (*), 1901-1902, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 764)
  - Wood, C. T., 1894 (Box 27, Folder 765)
  - Wood, Irving S., 1907 (Box 27, Folder 765)
  - Wood, John Seymour, 1894-1896, undated (Box 27, Folder 765)
  - Wood, Leonard, 1893, 1914, undated (Box 27, Folder 765)
  - Wood, Otis(*), 1914-1919 (Box 27, Folder 766)
  - Wood, Russell A., 1901 (Box 27, Folder 767)
  - Wood, Thomas D., 1894, 1911, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 767)
  - Wood, Washington, 1914 (Box 27, Folder 767)
  - Woodman, Francis Call, 1892, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 768)
  - Woodman, J. Edmund, 1905 (Box 27, Folder 768)
  - Woodruff, E. H., 1904 (Box 27, Folder 768)
  - Woodruff, George W., 1891-1909, undated (Box 27, Folder 768)
  - Woodruff, Timothy L., 1897 (Box 27, Folder 768)
  - Woodward, A. C., 1918 (Box 27, Folder 769)
  - Woodward, C. M., 1902 (Box 27, Folder 769)
  - Woodward, Rufus S., 1908, 1910 (Box 27, Folder 769)
  - Woodworth, Edward K., 1902 (Box 27, Folder 770)
  - Woodworth, Frank D., 1904-1906, 1909 (Box 27, Folder 770)
  - Woodyard, Edward D., 1919 (Box 27, Folder 770)
  - Woolsey, Theodore S.(*), 1896, 1900-1907 (Box 27, Folder 771)
  - World's Work (*), 1922-1924, undated (Box 27, Folder 772)
  - Wrenn, Everts, 1910-1911, 1914 (Box 27, Folder 773)
  - Wrenn, Robert D.(*), 1900-1921, undated (Box 27, Folder 774)
  - Wright & Ditson Co., 1893, 1908 (Box 27, Folder 775)
  - Wright, Beals C., 1899 (Box 27, Folder 775)
  - Wright, C. A., 1905 (Box 27, Folder 775)
  - Wright, Elizabeth A., 1902 (Box 27, Folder 775)
  - Wright, Henry P.(*), 1892-1895, 1900-1913 (Box 27, Folder 776)
  - Wright, William Burnet, Jr.(*), 1891-1896, 1900-1920 (Box 28, Folder 777)
  - Wrightington, Edgar N., 1894, 1902 (Box 28, Folder 778)
  - Writer, 1892 (Box 28, Folder 778)
  - Wurtenberg, William C., 1894 (Box 28, Folder 779)
  - Wurtz, Rudolf, 1894 (Box 28, Folder 779)
  - Wyeth, N. C., 1909 (Box 28, Folder 779)
  - Wylie, Edward A. Gill, Undated, 1906, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 779)
  - Yale Alumni Association:
    - Boston, 1901 (Box 28, Folder 780)
    - California, 1892-1893 (Box 28, Folder 780)
    - Colorado, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 780)
    - Long Island, 1892 (Box 28, Folder 780)
    - New Haven, 1888-1889 (Box 28, Folder 780)
    - New York City, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 780)
    - Northern California, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 780)
    - Portland (Oregon), 1924 (Box 28, Folder 780)
    - Western Massachusetts, 1911 (Box 28, Folder 780)
  - Yale Alumni Weekly (*), 1894-1907, 1909, 1911, 1917, undated (Box 28, Folder 781-790)
  - Yale Clubs:
    - Boston, 1902, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 791)
    - Chicago, 1903 (Box 28, Folder 791)
    - New Bedford, 1920 (Box 28, Folder 791)
    - New York City, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 791)
  - Yale Daily News (*), 1890-1891, 1897, 1902-1925, undated (Box 28, Folder 792)
  - Yale Field Corporation(*), 1881-1883, 1892-1907, undated (Box 28, Folder 793-794)
    Includes reports, Articles of Association, agreements and minutes of meetings.
  - Yale Financial Union(*), 1881-1883, 1892-1907, undated (Box 29, Folder 795-797)
    Includes financial statements.
  - Yale Publishing Association, 1911 (Box 29, Folder 798)
  - Yale Record, 1899 (Box 29, Folder 798)
  - Yale University Athletic Association(*), 1883-1884, 1890-1927, undated (Box 29, Folder 799-803)
    Includes constitution, by-laws, minutes of meetings, programs, contracts and agreements.
  - Yale University Athletic Association; minutes(*), 1906-1908, 1911-1914 (Box 29, Folder 804-807)
  - Yale University Baseball Association(*), 1875-1895, 1899-1910, undated (Box 29, Folder 808-812)
  - Yale University Basketball Association, 1899 (Box 29, Folder 813)
  - Yale University
    - Bi-centennial Celebration, 1901 (Box 29, Folder 814)
    - Bicycle Association, 1899 (Box 29, Folder 814)
  - Yale University Boat Club(*), 1882, 1886, 1894-1897, 1900-1903, 1906-1909, undated (Box 30, Folder 815-817)
    Includes governing rules, constitution, reports and agreements.
  - Yale University
    - Cross Country Team, 1900 (Box 30, Folder 818)
    - Department of Health, 1917 (Box 30, Folder 818)
  - Yale University Football Association(*), 1885, 1889, 1891-1896, 1899-1919, undated (Box 30, Folder 819-821)
    Reports, constitution, by-laws and articles of agreements.
  - Yale University Football Association, Ticket Department(*), 1906-1915, undated (Box 30, Folder 822)
  - Yale University Gymnasium(*), 1891, 1900-1910, undated (Box 30, Folder 823)
  - Yale University
    - Hockey Team, 1899, undated (Box 30, Folder 824)
    - Library, 1908, 1910-1912 (Box 30, Folder 824)
    - Press, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 824)
  - Yale University
    - School of Law, 1920 (Box 30, Folder 825)
    - School of Medicine, 1919 (Box 30, Folder 825)
  - Yale University, Secretary's Office(*), 1898, 1900-1917, undated (Box 30, Folder 826-832)
    Folder 826 includes reports and minutes of meetings.
  - Yale University
    - Sheffield Scientific School, 1900, 1902-1903, 1909, undated (Box 30, Folder 833)
      Includes Regulations of the Sheffield Scientific School.
    - Skating Rink, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 833)
    - Soccer Football Club, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 833)
  - Yale University
    - Tennis Association, 1901, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 834)
    - Track Team, 1891, [1895], 1901-1921 (Box 30, Folder 834)
      Includes Conditions governing Harvard-Yale contests for the University Track Athletic Cup, Constitution of the Yale University Track Association, and Minutes of the Track Cup Committee.
  - Yale University, Treasurer's Office(*), 1890-1902, 1916-1917 (Box 30, Folder 835)
    Includes annual reports of the Graduate Treasurer for 1890 and 1893.
  - Yale University
    - Wrestling Association, 1906 (Box 31, Folder 836)
    - Young Men's Christian Association, 1920 (Box 31, Folder 836)
  - Yates, C. H., 1888 (Box 31, Folder 837)
  - Yates, John L., 1916 (Box 31, Folder 837)
  - York, W. H., 1916 (Box 31, Folder 838)
  - Yost, Fielding H.(*), 1904-1925 (Box 31, Folder 838)
  - Young, B. C., 1893 (Box 31, Folder 839)
  - Young Folks Library, 1901, undated (Box 31, Folder 839)
  - Young, Fred, 1920 (Box 31, Folder 839)
  - Young, George H., 1889 (Box 31, Folder 839)
  - Young, H. Alfred, 1893 (Box 31, Folder 839)
  - Young, Horace L., 1902 (Box 31, Folder 839)
  - Young, James N., 1913-1914, 1916 (Box 31, Folder 839)
  - Young Men's Christian Association
    - Atlanta, Georgia, 1920 (Box 31, Folder 840)
    - Beverly, Massachusetts, 1920 (Box 31, Folder 840)
    - Derby, Connecticut, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 840)
    - Fall River, Massachusetts, 1917-1918, 1920 (Box 31, Folder 840)
    - New Britain, Connecticut, 1920 (Box 31, Folder 840)
    - New Haven, Connecticut, 1917 (Box 31, Folder 840)
    - Utica, New York, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 840)
    - Worcester, Massachusetts, 1922 (Box 31, Folder 840)
  - Young, Morrison, W., 1902 (Box 31, Folder 841)
  - Young, N. B., 1889 (Box 31, Folder 841)
  - Young, N. E., 1894 (Box 31, Folder 841)
  - Youth's Companion (*), 1892, 1899, 1910-1915 (Box 31, Folder 842)
  - Ziegler, Irving E., 1894 (Box 31, Folder 843)
  - Zimmerman, Charles H., 1917 (Box 31, Folder 843)
  - Zuppke, Robert C., 1915-1922 (Box 31, Folder 843)
  - Unidentified(*), 1886-1923, undated (Box 31, Folder 844-849)
- Writings, 1891 - 1925; Series II; 12.5 linear feet (30 boxes)
  The writings of Walter Camp constitute the second major portion of papers and are arranged by topic or type in six categories: athletics, physical fitness, general writings, aphorisms, poetry and miscellaneous writings. Articles on athletics, particularly football, and on physical fitness, are in the majority.
  Agreements and contracts with publishers, and reviews of some of his books, are also included in this series.
  Camp's poetry and aphorisms are largely undated and are not arranged in any particular order or by subject.
  Throughout the several sections of Series II is background material used by Walter Camp in preparing his articles, particularly on athletics and physical fitness. Consisting for the most part of articles written by others, statistics, etc., these folders are listed as "Research notes" in this register.
  - Football: history, 1891-1924 (Box 32, Folder 1-6)
  - Football: history, undated (Box 32, Folder 7-14)
  - Football: history, undated (Box 33, Folder 15-27)
  - Football: history, undated (Box 34, Folder 28-36)
  - Football: history: research notes, 1882-1904 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Football: review of the seasons, 1891-1903 (Box 34, Folder 38-42)
  - Football: review of the seasons, 1904-1924 (Box 35, Folder 43-53)
  - Football: review of the seasons, undated (Box 35, Folder 54-57)
  - Football: review of the seasons, undated (Box 36, Folder 58-68)
  - Football: review of the seasons, undated (Box 37, Folder 69-80)
  - Football: review of the seasons: research notes, 1876-1909, 1912-1922 (Box 37, Folder 81-82)
  - Football: review of the seasons: research notes, undated (Box 37, Folder 83)
  - Football: All America Teams: history, undated (Box 38, Folder 84)
  - Football: All America Teams, 1889-1924 (Box 38, Folder 85-107)
  - Football: All America Teams, undated (Box 38, Folder 108-110)
  - Football: rules, 1883-1889, 1893-1897, 1900-1910 (Box 39, Folder 111-126)
  - Football: rules, 1910-1925 (Box 40, Folder 127-135)
  - Football: rules, undated (Box 40, Folder 136-142)
  - Football: rules, undated (Box 41, Folder 143-147)
  - Football: rules: research notes, 1896-1909, undated (Box 41, Folder 148)
  - Football rules, printed and Spalding's Official Foot Ball Guide, 1876-1877, 1883, 1887-1894 (Box 41, Folder 149-150)
  - Football: Spalding's Official Foot Ball Guide, 1895-1903 (Box 41, Folder 151-153)
  - Football: Spalding's Official Foot Ball Guide, 1904-1909, 1911, 1913-1914, 1930, 1932-1933 (Box 42, Folder 154-158)
  - How to Play Football, 1894, 1909, 1921 (Box 42, Folder 159)
  - Football: Investigating Committee reports and comments, 1894 (Box 43, Folder 160)
  - Football: Investigating Committee questionnaire (Loveland)
    - Harvard University, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 161)
    - Princeton University, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 162)
    - Wesleyan-University, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 163)
    - Yale University, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 164)
  - Football Investigating Committee questionnaire -college/club (Camp)
    - Allegheny College, Amherst College, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 165)
    - Beloit College - Bucknell University, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 166)
    - California, University of - Cornell University, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 167)
    - Dartmouth College - Gettysburg College, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 168)
    - Harvard University, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 169-170)
    - Haverford College - Iowa State University, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 171)
    - Lafayette College, Lehigh College, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 172)
    - Maryville College - Minnesota, University of, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 173)
    - Nashville, University of - Nebraska, University of, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 174)
    - Oberlin College, Ohio Wesleyan University, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 175)
    - Pennsylvania, University of, 1893 (Box 43, Folder 176)
    - Princeton University, 1893 (Box 44, Folder 177-178)
    - Rutgers University, 1893 (Box 44, Folder 179)
    - Seattle Athletic Club - Swarthmore College, 1893 (Box 44, Folder 180)
    - Tennessee, University of - Tulane University, 1893 (Box 44, Folder 181)
    - Union College, United States Naval Academy, 1893 (Box 44, Folder 182)
    - Vanderbilt University, 1893 (Box 44, Folder 183)
    - Wabash College - Wisconsin, University of, 1893 (Box 44, Folder 184)
    - Yale University, 1893 (Box 44, Folder 185-186)
  - Football Investigating Committee questionnaire -high school (Camp)
    - Adams Academy - Albany High School, 1893 (Box 44, Folder 187)